AKM ELIAS

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A passionate and detail-oriented software engineer with two years of professional experience in javascript and javascript-based frameworks (React, Vue, Nodejs - express) and OOP(PHP), C++. A competitive programmer who loves to solve complex problems and make cool things.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

AuthLab, Sylhet (December 2021 - Present)

- Integrate CRM apps and payment gateways.
- Add customer-requested features and bug-solving to the existing market-leading product.
- Redesign and improves UI.
- Work closely with Support and marketing teams.
- Use Javascript (VUE) on frontend and OOP(PHP) on the backend

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Bengal Infotech , Sylhet (November 2020 - November, 2021)

- Made apps for vendors
- Was responsible for solving and implementing business logic.
- Worked with seniors closely.
- Used Javascript(React) and Express(Nodejs) GraphQl, MongoDB as tech stack.

JR. SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CC LTD, Dhaka (September 2019 - March 2020)

- Written API Documentation
- Test and fix Issues.
- Worked on UI
- Used Postman, Git, Javascript, Html, CSS



+8801746065555

www.akmelias.com

Sylhet, Bangladesh

EDUCATION

METROPOLITAN UNIVERSITY SYLHET

2014 - 2019

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science and Engineering

SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES

- Complex problem solving and Analytical thinking.
- Deep understanding of Data structure and algorithms.
- Generating dynamic and multiple solutions
- Experience in Team work.
- Javascript(React, Vue), Nodejs, PHP
 OOP(PHP), C++, MySQL, Git,
 NOSQL, Html5, CSS3
- Good at English speaking, reading and writing